<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Path Finder</string>
    <string name="title_activity_solution">Find My Path</string>
    <string name="large_text">
        https://raphaelraymondproduct@gmail.com
        Path Finder
1.	Introduction
Path Finder is a game and a problem solving tool for TSP (Transportation Sales Problem).
Shortest Path Game provide some points (let say stations) for you to find the shortest path to move round (to all point) the points. Imagine a problem of vaccine to be distributed at various airports and back to the main station, with aim of trying to minimize the cost. Tip: when playing the game aim at for a cyclic path, it will provide shortest path on this way.
Find My Path (Solving tool for TSP) you will provide either the locations or distances between the locations (or cost) and the App will give you the shortest path to fellow. If have an image of the map of locations you can easily load the map (snap or gallery) and point at desired location to which want to find the shortest path.
Choosing input method:
•	Choose location by typing if you have the coordinate and the distance (cost) equals the displacement (or going by road is equal going by air) --- location important, graph important.
•	Choose location by image when you have the map image with location. Note location generated are equivalent to actual location.
•	Choose distance when the distances or cost are known and coordinate are unknown.  Cost is important, graph is not important. The graph

2.	Operation (User guide)
Open app donate to support the developer.
A.	Playing the game.
Firstly open the app, if don’t like sound disable it at top right side icon. Press Shortest Path (game model) Select new for game in the popup as new user and the initial level will be start. If you are not a new user pressing new will take to place where you can start from level that you have unlock.  Press resume to continue from previously played game. When game is over you can only start new but have the chance of choosing higher level than initial but the scores will not  can only be gain.
There are Alphabet indicating various cities. Click on them directly to indicate interest of starting or moving to them. The one clicked on will have a different circle color round it. Click the next destination and a path with be drawn. Continue to your desire points until you exhaust the points. After exhausting the points you will prompt with win or lose; when loose up to three times game over will be replace with lose. When you win, you can go to next or you can return to see your path before moving. When you lose, you try again or return like as in win.  Click play button if you wish to resume after pressing return in lose, win or game over. Note the current location will always have its own distinct color apart from already visited. Click or already visited city to undo ( that means attempting to select already selected city will cause it to deselect).
Menu (menu icon) have the preference setting about sound, keyboard, refreshing point on try again, and using timing. It also contain highest score ever played.

B.	Solving a TSP problem
Open the App choose Find My Path to the solution model will be visible for to work on. Select your input method by click on the current input method which now help you to toggle between “add by location”, “add by loading map” and “add by distance”. After changing the desire input method click of plus icon (top right) to add. You can always clear all by clicking on clear icon (top left). After adding the problem click on the bottom right icon to get the shortest path.
Adding by image is not incremental, that means when you add an image you are require to finish adding all the location before clicking finish icon. Also note you load an image and toggle add and using the add switch (bottom left). When you are done adding the point you can then press bottom right icon as finish or the one in action bar menu. Once you click add (plus icon) when “add by Loading map” is active the exiting data will be discarded.
Adding Location select it to be active the click the add icon. The next view will require you to put latitude and longitude plus the location and the location name. Click finish when done adding the first location (it will take you back to previous view but the location been added) Now click add again to add another location. Same process continues till you exhaust your points (locations). ( if there exist any data clear it to start fresh problem when adding a new problem). Once again when you are done adding the point you can then press bottom right icon as finish or the one in action bar menu.
Adding by distances or cost, select add by distance. Next, click add icon and type only city name in the next view and click finish when done just like in add by location. The next will require you to add the city name and it distance to the first.  The third will require you to add city name and its distance to the first and second. Repeatedly you add all the cities and their distances as the number distances increment.
Note a problem must have up three cities at minimum.

    </string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="action_save">Save</string>
    <string name="action_open">Open</string>
    <string name="dyn">Dynamic</string>
    <string name="knn">K-Nearest Neighbour</string>
    <string name="gen">Genetic</string>
    <string name="auto">Auto(from above)</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="select_alg">Select Algorithm</string>
    <string name="title_activity_addL">Add Locations</string>
    <string name="addByDistances">Add by Distances</string>
    <string name="addByLoadingMap">Add by Loading Map</string>
    <string name="addByLocation">Add by Location</string>
    <string name="select_input_method">Select Input Method</string>
    <string name="empty_fields">Empty fields</string>
    <string name="latitude">\"Latitude \"</string>
    <string name="longitude">\"Longitude \"</string>
    <string name="name_is_empty">Name is empty</string>
    <string name="okay">Okay</string>
    <string name="empty">"Empty "</string>
    <string name="not_a_number">Not a number</string>
    <string name="win">Win</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="game_over">Game Over</string>
    <string name="new_">New</string>
    <string name="welcome">Welcome</string>
    <string name="resume">Resume</string>
    <string name="shortest_path">"Shortest path "</string>
    <string name="Level">\"Level \"</string>
    <string name="finished">Finished</string>
    <string name="cities_small">Cities too small to be a program</string>
    <string name="un_init">Unable to initialised, add distances or locations</string>
    <string name="cities_not_added">Cities are not added</string>
    <string name="input_empty_start_problem">Inputs empty start a new problem</string>
    <string name="error">\"Error \"</string>
    <string name="city_name">City Name</string>
    <string name="go">Go</string>
    <string name="menu">menu</string>
    <string name="level">Level</string>
    <string name="time">Time</string>
    <string name="play">Play</string>
    <string name="zoom_out">zoom out</string>
    <string name="zoom_in">zoom in</string>
    <string name="scores">Scores</string>
    <string name="donate">Donate</string>
    <string name="find_my_path">Find My Path</string>
    <string name="play_game">Play Game</string>
    <string name="solution_model">Solution model</string>
    <string name="sound_toggle">Sound toggle</string>
    <string name="total_distances_cost">Total distances(cost)</string>
    <string name="locations">Locations</string>
    <string name="matrix_representation_of_distances">Matrix representation of distances</string>
    <string name="visualised">Visualised</string>
    <string name="refresh">refresh</string>
    <string name="add">add</string>
    <string name="solve">solve</string>
    <string name="city">City</string>
    <string name="empty_field">empty field</string>
    <string name="close">Close</string>
    <string name="you_lose">You lose</string>
    <string name="return_">Return</string>
    <string name="refresh_points_always">Refresh points always</string>
    <string name="actions_sounds">Actions Sounds</string>
    <string name="keys">Keys</string>
    <string name="background_sound">Background Sound</string>
    <string name="highest_score">Highest score</string>
    <string name="timing">Timing</string>
    <string name="take_photo">Take Photo</string>
    <string name="choose_from_gallery">Choose from Gallery</string>
    <string name="ad_photo">Add Photo!</string>
    <string name="permission_msg">Oh you have not accepted permission for the App to access your storage</string>
    <string name="accept_now">Accept now</string>
    <string name="permission_not_set">Permission not set</string>
    <string name="level_lock">This level is locked</string>
    <string name="load_map">Load map</string>
    <string name="undo">undo</string>
    <string name="ad_some_points">"Add some points "</string>
    <string name="saveByLocation">Save locations</string>
    <string name="saveByDistances">save distances</string>
    <string name="openByLocation">Open Tsp Locations</string>
    <string name="openByDistances">Open Tsp distances</string>
    <string name="b_played">Best played so far</string>
    <string name="share">Share</string>
    <string name="current_game">Current Game</string>
    <string name="start_from_level">Start From Level</string>
    <string name="start_game">Start Game</string>
    <string name="help">Help</string>
    <string name="edit">"edit "</string>
    <string name="delete">delete</string>
    <string name="highestStageGame">Highest stage game</string>
    <string name="currentStageGame">Current stage Game</string>
    <string name="unable_to_share">Unable to share</string>
    <string name="warn_over">To continue using the app, Please update</string>
    <string name="update_now">Update Now</string>
    <string name="warn_msg">Update app or you won\'t be able to use it after using the app </string>
    <string name="time_s_">time(s)</string>
    <string name="sound_enable">Sound enable</string>
    <string name="sound_disable">Sound disable</string>
</resources>